After processing the two videos I won, a video of the deck up lyrics clear was also done.
Thank you for your attention.
érieur
Yes, it has begun!
Itria's
I did it! The road to Pokemon master!
This time, I got a Pokemon card 151
And this time 151
Darn!
I have a file.
The cow is so cute in the river
This Pokémon Card 151 is
This card contains 151 Pokemon of the first generation.
This file is
It seems to be a special file with the number from 1 to 151, so the card itself is numbered by type.
The cards themselves are numbered by type.
This time, the cards are numbered by book number, which is very special.
I usually watch videos, but I don't know much about recent Pokémon.
If you usually watch videos but don't know much about the latest Pokemon, you may be interested in this card.
If you usually watch videos but don't know much about the latest Pokémon, you may be able to find Pokémon that are very familiar to you.
Now that we have this special file, I wonder if I can collect 151 Pokémon.
I'd like to see if I can collect 151 Pokemon with this special file.
Yay!
I've been really looking forward to this ever since 151 was announced.
I've been looking forward to it so much since 151 was announced, and I've been playing games and the latest ones.
I know the latest Pokemon, but...
but I'm more familiar with the Pokemon that have been around for a long time.
There are a lot of cards I want to get this time, so I'm looking forward to it!
I'll go on with my game now.
It's been a long time since I got a file.
I always put them in a case, so I haven't done so recently.
It's so cute!
And there's a silhouette of a Pokemon on it.
Let's take a look at what's inside.
Wow!
Amazing!
Look!
Ta-da!
They're numbered!
The silhouettes of Pokémon and their numbers!
Can't you see it?
They're a little overlapped here.
23, 21...
Each one of them is numbered.
If you file each one of them
When Pokémon gather, you can see
Wow, don't you want to do a quiz with these Pokemon silhouettes?
Ha-ha-ha-ha
I know, all of them!
It's fun!
It's fun just to look at them, even though they're silhouettes.
Well, I'd like to open the packs right away.
Okay, so I'm going to open the first box right away!
As for this time, there are a lot of Pokemon from the first generation.
There are too many cards that I want to have.
SandSandSandSandSandSandSandSandSandSandSandSandSandSandSandSandSandSandSand
I like Coil Coil.
Everyone is so bright!
I can't help but notice the familiar faces.
Monita's cute.
What's this?
This is a normal one.
Do you know what this is? It's a Monster Ball mirror.
There's only one Master Ball mirror in each box.
I'm really looking forward to seeing what kind of Pokémon it's going to be!
Platters
Logarts
Asaihorn.
It's nice because I can use it with confidence.
Utsudom.
Wethorn.
Wethorn. It's cute.
This one's really funny too.
It's so cute.
You see that? Can you see me here, guys?
It's kind of hard to tell where he is.
Wethorn always plays a funny song every time they release a card.
Wow, I love it! There are so many old Pokemon here!
but I haven't played the first Pokemon because I'm not of the generation.
But maybe... there are a lot of people who have played Pokemon.
Oh, Brolinga...
Wow, I miss Boober!
This is a Monster Ball!
Oh, here's Lucky!
Lucky's so cute!
It's got a really interesting trait... a lucky bonus.
Side? It's called a Pokemon card.
If you get all the sides, you win.
That's how the game is played.We have several trainers this time.
I think the most popular one is
I think Erika is the most popular one.
Erika's siblings are very popular.
The card named "Erika's brother" is very popular.
Pikachu
Club
Munky
Sleeper
Lubmen and Reyka
I swallowed it.
Sleeper.
Masterball! Look at that.
Oh, my God, it's so good!
You know what I like about it?
The Master Ball is purple!
That's why this super-type Pokémon
MasterBall came to this super-type Pokémon.
I like it.
I thought it was hot, and I swooned a little.
And...
Pamex-EX is here.
It's great!
I think there's maybe three families
I think there's three families in the Pamex line this time.
I'm kind of looking forward to it.
I'd like to have a little bit of that.
Good, good, good.
Oh! That's so cute!
Isn't that Eazy?
Too cute.
What? ! Raichu is too cute!
What! I want to clip this to my cell phone!
Well, this time
There are so many cards I want to get
If it's SR...
I want Erika's true identity.
There is another card called "Sakaki's Charisma
but there is another card called "Sakaki's Charisma
I want Sakaki's Charisma more than Erika's Identity if it's SR.
I want Sakaki's charisma more than Erika's identity.
That card is so cool!
Are you guys serious? Why?
I know some of you might say...
I want Sakaki's charisma.
I mean...
There's also something called Art Rare.
Art Rare.
I don't care what you wear.
But I want Mewtwo
Pikachu and Kodak
I especially like Pikachu and Kodak.
I've been wanting to get Pikachu ever since the design was announced.
I've been wanting to get it ever since it was announced.
I've been wanting to get this one for a long time.
Pikachu
Art Rare
Isn't it great?
It's too timely.
Look at this.
I got a Mewtwo Art Rare.
I told him I wanted a Mewtwo Art Rare.
It came in about 0.5 seconds.
What do you think?
This isn't a special Art Rare?
Don't you get it?
Mewtwo.
He's so cool!
I'm so happy.
We've got 53 more Art Rares.
Hitokage...
Shigidane...
And these guys, too.
I don't care who they wear.
I like Lizard. I want Lizard.
You'd look so cute in a Hitokage.
Booster.
I want it so much!
It's so cute!
Om Knight
It's too sparty!
Art Rare!
And here comes Sigimana EX!
It's good, no EXs.
It's so good!
Last time it was a god pull!
I don't know if you guys saw my last video.
I don't know if you saw it.
I don't know if you saw it, but...
If you haven't seen it, you should check it out.
Last time, I had a super god pull.
After that...
I was really worried that I'd have to face some unforeseen misfortune.
I was worried that I'd meet with some uncontrollable misfortune.
But I'm living happily ever after.
I'm fine.
Since you were so worried about me.
I'm glad you're all...
I don't know if we'll have that kind of luck this time.
I may not have it this time.Maybe not this time.
I spent so much last time.
Maybe not this time.
I don't know if I can count on it this time.
But we've already done
I've already done about half of them.
Monjarra has an art rare too, right?
So cute!
It's a Puclin EX.
Look how cute it is!
Puclin, Puclin, Puclin...
It's always not cute.
One Nikki.
Cute.
Beedle is smiling so much.
I've never seen him smile like this.
Too cute!
It's a mirror of Rokon.
Rokon and Q-Con...
The character design is really good.
Eeeeee!
Bye bye!
I knew it... I feel like this channel is so loved by Rougera.
Kero se!
Yama... I love Rouge la...
When I gave it to Yama, Rouge la came over.
She was making a fuss.
But she's not here today.
Wow, I wish she was here!
If Yama saw this video and said.
I'd like to give it to her.
I'll give it to him.
I'll give it to you if Yama sees this video and asks for it.
There's also Lizardon and New.
This one is really cool.
Wow, Matadogus...
Wow, Nidoking is nice!
I like it. I like it.
I'm sure it's familiar.
Yamaman is cute!
Oh, I wonder if there are 3 art rares in the box.
I wonder if there's one more.
Ew.
But I got Mewtwo, so I'll be pretty happy if I get the one I'm looking for.
I'll be pretty happy if I get another Pikachu or Kodak.
I'd be happy with a Hitokage, too.
Oh!
It's Kamuel!
So cute!
I knew it's good, isn't it? 5,300 yen is good.
It's so cute, look.
This ocean sparkle, maybe.
I think you can see it in the video.
Isn't it beautiful? Isn't it amazing?
It's like the texture of a movie.
Wow, it's so pretty.
Wow, I like Kamuel.
Wow, Mewtwo is so cool!
Is this the coolest thing you've ever seen?
No, it's cool.
Mewtwo, no matter what kind of Pokémon they come out with...
Mewtwo is one of the top 10 coolest Pokémon of all time.
I think it's one of the top 10, right?
I've always thought it was really cool.
Oh, the bike path.
The bike path!
The studio's here.
Persian, yes!
I've got a special art rare card called "Sakaki's Charisma".
Special Art Rare!
Persian is cuddling up to me.
It's an illustration of Persian cuddling up.
It's so good, I really want it!
Come on, come on!
Oh! Oh! Here it comes! Here it is!
It's Garula EX!
This is a fun deck to use!
It's a bit like a Garula team.
There's a move called "Machine Gun Punch".
You throw a coin 4 times, and the number of times it's face up multiplied by 100 damage.
It does 400 damage, so it's got a lot of firepower.
It doesn't have 400 HP.
So you can almost knock him out.
It's very interesting.
You can make a deck to try your luck.
No, I want to make this deck.
Very good, very interesting!
Last one.
Wow! I miss Caracalla!
I miss Porgo!
So cute!
Nyorobon and...
Ah! Here comes Kameer!
Ah! That's the last one.
The end!
End of the first box!
Yes, so the result of the first box is
The result of the first box was like this
SR came with Rugula EX, andSR came the Ruggera EX.
This mirror of Master Ball came Sleeper
Art Rare came Mewtwo if you don't think of Kameru.
I wanted Mewtwo Art Rare so much!
I'm super happy!
Well, I'll tell you about it this time.
I've got the files, too.
I'm going to file it in the book number.
Okay, so...
Ta-da!
I've filed them.
There are a lot of them here.
I've got a lot of them here, but the first number is the most common.
I'm surprised there's so many of them.
I don't see any three-digit numbers here.
Lizard Lizard wasn't here.
The numbers in the back are pretty much all gone.
Mew, Freezer...
There were quite a few that weren't there.
I'm going to open up the second box a little bit.
I'd like to fill all of these.
I'd like to open the second box.
Oh, I forgot
There are some love cusps today.
But after filing it earlier
I'd like to have some Pokémon that haven't appeared
You know, like Freezer Thunder.
Mew EX hasn't come in, come to think of it.
It's the highlight of this pack.
Because it's Mew this time.
If Mew-EX doesn't come, I might be in a bit of trouble.
And Pikachu.
Oh! Pikachu!
You're here. Oh, my God.
Well, you're cute, and I don't care how many of you there are.
Well, I'm a little dubious.
Well, I don't care. You're cute.
And Art Rare, because I want Pikachu and Kodak.
Well, it means there are 3 cards in a box.
I'd like to draw two of them.
I wonder if they'll come... Oh! Oh, here it comes!
It's Showers! So cute!
Yeah, and Buiz, too. I've only been able to pull a few boosters.
I love Showers. I love Showers. I love Showers.
We're getting more and more of them.
I don't know about that.
I wonder if you guys are the type of person who fills in the picture books when you play games.
I don't fill them up at all.
Ah! Mr. Sungdo!
Go on! More and more are coming! You're so cute!
I'm more interested in making them stronger.
I'm not the type of person who collects all kinds of Pokemon
I'm not the type of person who plays games
I'm more the type who likes battles.
Dodeman
OmStar, OmStar, OmStar Ball
Oh! Oh!
Cute! Look!
Here comes the Trex EX SR! So cool!
This EX SR is so cool, seriously!
Eh, but it's not a hydro pump, which is a bit surprising.
Swing Cannon something or other.
No, but the Lizard EX didn't come.
I've been waiting for that SR for a while...
But it's nice.
I think that 5 or 3 machines have their own unique qualities.
I'm not...
Let's EVE!
Ah! Leftovers!
Oh, it's a Monster Ball mirror.
I put it in the enemy and it's free equipment.
Ah! It's the Lizard! Here it comes!
Lizard! It's here!
If the Lizard comes, we'll have all five or three.
Lizard!
Kitakage, Weber.
Ah! Ghost!
Ah, it's the Monster Ball.
No, it would have been a little better if the Master Ball came in a Ghost.
Hey! Rouge Rai EX!
Here it comes.
As before, this time it's a regular version of Rouglai-EX.
But it seems like there's quite a few Pokémon here that I haven't seen before.
Or maybe it's just my imagination.
Ah! I heard it's Nyoromon.
There was a Gnomon and a Gnomon and a Gnomon, but I don't think there was a Gnomon here.
Lil' Reed.
Ah! Oh! That's Toutawamon.
I don't think I've ever seen that before.
Oh!
Gorky's.
I love the subtle nuance in this one.
So cute!
Gorky's helping me move. It's so cute.
How is it? It's really good.Omnite is here! Art Rare
Nah, but it's cute.
Maybe one more art rare.
Oh! Oh! Here it comes! It's a Thunder EX!
It's so cool! That's awesome!
It's so good! It's so good!
I'm so happy.
Oh! Oh, my God! I've never seen that before! Erica!
Oh! She's cute.
Short girls are cute, aren't they?
I haven't seen Kairyu either.
He's a normal card, but he's so cute.
Here we go, here we go, here we go.
Oh! Is that a little Masterball in the Vero Linga?
I don't know.
He's so cute!
What? There's one more Art Rare left.
I wonder what's coming.
Oh! Here it comes! Garula!
No, I think you mean build a deck, don't you? What's this?
No, I haven't drawn any mills.
That's a big problem.
What? What's the last of the art rares?
Eh! I want Pikachu Korak, but I'm happy to wear any of them!
I'm happy even with that punky.
Ah! Monjura-chan! Cute!
So cute! Look! Artlea's Mongulas are here!
This Mongulas swinging on the swing by herself is so cute!
I'll open the last pack.
Yozo, oh! Nosy, nosy, muster!
Yozo, oh! Nosy, the second one.
Yes! Midrina!
Yes! I think it looks like this.
The second box looks like this!
Well, I personally think
I think that the EX SRs of the three families are...
Not only Kamex, but also Nizardon and Sigivaran.
They're really cool, so I'm really excited about them.
When I first saw the Monjura swinging on its own, I really liked it.
It's so cute, I love it.
I'm a little sad that I didn't get the art rarity I wanted, but...
And now Garula's here.
I'd like to see it again.
Yes! So, the filing is done!
Ta-da! I've been filing a lot like this.
It's all coming together...
Isn't it amazing? It's amazing, but seriously...
But seriously, it's hard to fill up all of them.
First of all, Nizardon and Nizardon-EX.
The EXs are pretty hard to come by.
So we couldn't fill all of them.
I'd like to fill in all of them.
I'd like to fill all of them.
But this one, this one is ELEVU.
It's not an EX, it's a noval.
There's not one piece that's not here.
I'd like to have just a little bit of Ereboo.
It's Ereboo. New EX hasn't come either.
I don't have 8 cards!
Two of these cards are supposed to be normal.
I'd like to fill them.
I'd like to fill it up, actually.
It's going to take me a bit of time this time.
I was going to finish with 2 boxes...
But I decided to fill them in somehow!
So, I've added the third box with the hidden boxes.
Well, there are 20 more packs to go!
I opened the 20 packs with a bomb!
All of them!
Well, EX might be a little difficult.
But I'd like to pull Ereboo and Kairyu.
I'd like to pull them out!
I already know what I want.
I'd like to take a look at them in a little bit of a blast!
Ereboo.
Oh! First Kyotapi Art Rare!
Oh, I'm so happy!
Oh, here it comes! Express EX!
Yay!
This is what I wanted!
Oh, Omnite, seriously.
There's like 6 of everything in there.
The other day, in the video.
I drew the decks that everyone else was using.
It was really interesting, and there were a lot of unexpected decks.
Well, in the current environment, there is no such thing as the strongest deck.
Everyone is strong in their own way.
Woo! White Dragon Art Rare is so cute!Ohachi, thank you very much!
Wow, I can file.
Ooh!
Aah!
Cute, isn't it?
Wow!
I just hit the biggest jackpot I've ever hit here.
The water types love me.
Why are you leaving?
Hey!
What? Huh?
Shut up!
Seriously, if we don't get a Mew in this pack, it's not worth talking about.
I'm so happy!
How did they do this with the Kairyu magic?
I'm going to file it right away!
Arbok-EX is in!
Cucumber EX.
Here.
This way...
Elevoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo.
I knew it! These two are the best. We need more of them.
And last but not least... No, I'm lying!
Kaeli, you were so close.
Mewin-X is in, and we've filled 151.
One, two, three, and maybe four...
We didn't fill it. Four Pokémon filled it.
But, you know... I think we filled it up pretty well.
No, it's beautiful. Fun, fun, fun. Let me see.
Amazing!
Well, the result is... I couldn't get 4 more Pokémon...
But it was so much fun to see them all coming together.
I'm really satisfied.
Thank you very much for watching!
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating!
And please don't forget to leave a comment!
Bye bye!
undefined